Surbhi Rathod

Sadar Bazar Gandhwani, Distt- Dhar (M.P.) Email:- surbhirathod38@gmail.com

Mobile Number:- 8878410407

Android Developer with over 3 years 4 months of app development experience in a broad range of industries, including social media, seeding system, entertainment, and management. Solid understanding of full mobile and software development life cycles, UIX, web analytics, changing web standards, and Agile methodologies. Dedicated to continuously developing, implementing, and adopting new technologies to maximize development efficiency and produce innovative applications.

Android Development Knowledge

- Good Understanding App Development cycle and Android SDK
- Use of open-source library with Gradle system
- Understand Android UI/UX design principles and Patterns
- Experience with third-party libraries and APIs
- Ability to work with web services on the Android platform (consuming REST APIs) and related
- APIs and Push Notification Experience and Firebase (Database)
- Flutter Technology (IOS and Android)
- User Experience Design
- Mobile Development Life Cycle
- Native Android Development
- Professional Experience

Android Application Developer (Flutter Developer) 03/07/2019 – currently

Hajela Info System Pvt. Ltd. (NICT/Wood Apple Resources Pvt. Ltd.) Indore

Meri Dukan:- Meri Dukan is an online Kirana store. users can order Kirana products through a mobile phone at home and can get the product on the customer's doorstep. Developed Meri Dukan Application in Flutter technology.

Play Store Link:-

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.woodapple.meridukan App Store Link:- https://apps.apple.com/in/app/meri-dukan/id1479688182

Dawai4u: Dawai4u is an online medicine store. users can add their prescriptions in Application and if available these medicines so users can order medicine through a mobile phone at home and can get the medicine on the customer's doorstep.

Developed Dawai4U Application in Flutter technology.

Play store link:- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.dawai4u

Android Application Developer (Flutter Developer) 01/08/2017 – 27/04/2019 FODUU.COM Indore

• Work as part of a team to define and implement solutions in alignment with FODUU.COM.

- Developed Enrich Asia Social media Application. play store link:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.enrich.asia
- Developed Foduu HomeAutomation Application. play store link:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.foduu.foduuiot.
- Developed Tongabible Book Application.

play store link:- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.livingstonit.koetohitapukatoa.

- Developed Anna Health and Beauty Application in Flutter technology. play store link:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.annahealthbeauty.annagealthbeauty.
- Design and implement services, applications, and frameworks for mobile platforms to how users interact with content, integrate solutions into innovative core technologies and frameworks.
- Develop software supporting next-generation digital technologies; create and prototype solutions and proof of concepts to demonstrate innovations viability.

IOS Application:-

• Developed Anna Health and Beauty Application in Flutter technology.

Android Application Developer (Flutter Developer) 01/07/2016 –29/07/2017

Oswal Computers & Computers Pvt. Ltd. Indore

- Developed JanAadhaar System Application user can order PVC Aadhar Card Form home and can get that card at this doorstep.
- Aadhaar Seeding System, In this App Aadhaar no can be seeded with BOI bank account number.
- MIS System Application Managing PVC card details, Cash System details, Shop wise Amount Details. Developed GST SATH App, In this application showing GST services and what about GST.

Education

- 72% in Bachelor of Engineering (IT), JIT Borawan Khargone (M.P.)
- 50% in H.H.C(2011) from Seven Day High School Gandhwani Distt:- Dhar(M.P.)
- 53% in S.S.C.(2009) from Seven Day High School Gandhwani Distt:- Dhar(M.P.)

Technical Skills

• Java, Android NDK, XML, JSON, REST, API, HTML, Basic knowledge of MVVM, Flutter, Dart.

Declaration

I hereby assure that the above-given details of me are true and correct to my belief and best of my knowledge.

Date:-

Place:-